

GUILHERME VAZ

CONTACT



guilhermeolivaaz@gmail.com



+55(82) 98147-8577



portfolio-drab-pi.vercel.app



Avenida Menino Marcelo, 5585, Maceió, AL, Brazil

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Universidade Federal de

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Advanced English Basic Spanish Adobe Photoshop Figma

SOCIAL



github.com/guilherme-vaz



linkedin.com/in/guilhermevaz-273023132/

Front-end developer

ABOUT

I am a 24 years old front-end developer with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science. I had the opportunity to work on a few projects during my academic life, creating interfaces and coding several simple sites as a hobby. I've worked as a front-end developer in a team with a designer and a content producer in the creation of a new startup focused on web development. Now I am looking for a chance to use the knowledge acquired both in courses and in my projects to grow professionally.

Git

EXPERTISE

HTML Responsive Design CSS Python Sass Django JavaScript

React

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Universidade Federal de Alagoas | Fev 2019 a Junho 2019

- Developed the design of a website and an app.
- Planned and created Instagram posts for a campus newspaper.

FREELANCER

Upwork | Dez 2020 - 2021

I do some web development work.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Vybe Studio Ltd | Dez 2020 - 2021

• Development of startup's landing page using the qualifications mentioned above.